Justice is a quick draw.
Dawn Rider is a action, western film directed by Terry Miles.
A gripping story of vengeance and passion set in the American West.
When the father of gunslinger John Mason is shot to death by masked bandits,
Mason sets out with guns blazing to track down those who killed him.
During his quest, he finds himself involved in a grim love triangle when he falls for
Alice, the determined and beautiful woman also adored by John’s best friend.
Based on the timeless John Wayne adventure, Dawn Rider is a riveting
saga of retribution, duty and valor in the American West.
Pop, played by Donald Sutherland.
John, played by Christian Slater.
Alice, played by Jill Hennessy.
Rudd, played by Lochlyn Munro.
Sheriff Cobb, played by Adrian Hough.
Bragg, played by G. Michael Gray.
Dawn Rider is a 2012 Canadian-American Western film starring
Christian Slater, Jill Hennessy and Donald Sutherland.
It is a remake of the 1935 John Wayne film The Dawn Rider.
The tone is intense.